hi friends welcome back to my channel if
it's your first time here make sure you
do me a favor and hit that subscribe
button and turn on your notifications
today I'm going to do a product review I
have had this Kitchen Aid attachment for
several months now and I just now got
around to using it so I wanted to use it
for the first time on camera so I can
show you guys whether or not it's worth
it to purchase it or whether or not you
should leave it on the shelf check it
out so of course it comes with a manual
in English and Spanish so here's the
book I really like that it breaks down
the parts medium Sharia course
slicing large food pusher the release
lever attachment housing and a small
food pusher and let's look at the parts
here actually this goes here just super
nifty okay so this is the part that
looks up to the actual KitchenAid mixer
oh my god all right and then of course
we have our various
so we will we'll use these today and
practical and real time so I'm going to
use for the cheese the large food pusher
so put it in there it's gonna come down
the book is super super helpful so I'm
making mac and cheese today that's why
I'm using this some B's on display I put
it in here then I lock it and that locks
it in
alright so then I'll put just show you
guys so I put the other part on here
screw it in
it's not that hard but it does take a
second to get so now this is where we're
gonna feed the I'm doing cheese and then
these are the blades so it also comes
with these two other I don't need it
because you see that to this smaller so
I'm going to put the cheese in once I
had the cheese this part of make more
sense but this is the inner tube that's
the inner
[Music]
that really all right
Okubo I just have it on the first one
which is stir and that's fast enough so
let's test it on I'm a testing on a bet
so this is on a faster level flying
everywhere just a little more than I
thought
this is on
for but I think I'll keep it on the
lower levels
[Music]
overall I love this product and I would
highly recommend it for you to use
not just the shred cheese but it's a
slicer and everything on there but this
is like this is amazing so I'm
officially done and I think the cleanup
is gonna be pretty seamless you just put
this here
[Music]
twist it
oh yeah you can see it so you have to
twist it and of course is still a little
debris though and then I unhook this
part and then I wash it so the cleanup
is gonna be pretty good because it
doesn't come up a lot on the inside
which I was really concerned about and
then it was not much a lot left which
means that this product does its job
so cool thank you so much for watching
my product review for the Kitchen Aid
slicer attachment it gets a two thumbs
up from me so it is definitely just
peachy make sure you comment down below
if you would like me to review a product
or if you'd like to send me a product
make sure you send an email to the
information described below thanks again
so much and I will see you next time bye
you